weeno.com 2013-05-19

# Privacy Statement

##  Privacy Statement for Weeno.com 

**Weeno.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Weeno.com ](http://www.weeno.com/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. 

####  Advertisers 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

####  Registration Forms 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, background information, website), and unique identifiers (like their email address). 

The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Personal information such as name, background information and website are associated with your submitted articles and will be publically viewable by the Weeno community. You may choose to submit articles anonymously, however a valid email address is required. However, your email address will remain confidential. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Unique identifiers (such as email addresses) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Weeno.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

####  Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
